"use strict";(self.webpackChunkquiz_app=self.webpackChunkquiz_app||[]).push([[103],{103:e=>{e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"What does EC2 stand for in AWS?","answers":[{"text":"Elastic Cloud Computing","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Elastic Container Service","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Elastic Compute Cloud","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Elastic Cloud Container","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is an EC2 instance?","answers":[{"text":"A relational database service","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A virtual server in the cloud","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A managed container service","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A file storage service","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which AWS service allows you to scale EC2 instances automatically based on demand?","answers":[{"text":"Amazon S3","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon RDS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Amazon EBS","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) in the context of EC2?","answers":[{"text":"A security group for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A virtual private cloud (VPC) configuration","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A template for EC2 instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"A type of EC2 instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of an EC2 security group?","answers":[{"text":"To store data in Amazon S3","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To manage EC2 instance storage","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To define firewall rules for EC2 instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To configure load balancing for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which protocol is commonly used for connecting to Linux-based EC2 instances?","answers":[{"text":"RDP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"SSH","isCorrect":true},{"text":"HTTPS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"FTP","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of Elastic Load Balancing (ELB) in the context of EC2?","answers":[{"text":"To distribute incoming network traffic across multiple EC2 instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To automatically create and configure EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To provide persistent block-level storage volumes for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To manage user identities and access to EC2 instances","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which AWS service allows you to store and retrieve data in a scalable and durable manner and is often used with EC2 instances?","answers":[{"text":"Amazon RDS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon S3","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Amazon EBS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon DynamoDB","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of an EC2 key pair?","answers":[{"text":"To define security groups for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To create Amazon S3 buckets","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To encrypt data on EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To securely connect to EC2 instances using SSH","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the maximum number of Elastic IP addresses that you can associate with an EC2 instance by default?","answers":[{"text":"1","isCorrect":false},{"text":"5","isCorrect":false},{"text":"10","isCorrect":false},{"text":"5 (but can be increased by requesting an increase)","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"In AWS, what is the purpose of EC2 instance types (e.g., t2.micro, m5.large)?","answers":[{"text":"To specify the EC2 instance\'s color","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To define the geographic region where the EC2 instance is launched","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To determine the hardware of the host computer for the EC2 instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To specify the characteristics of the EC2 instance (e.g., CPU, memory, storage)","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"Which storage option is suitable for frequently accessed data and is often used as the root volume for EC2 instances?","answers":[{"text":"Amazon EBS","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Amazon S3","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon RDS","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Amazon Glacier","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of an EC2 instance metadata service?","answers":[{"text":"To store and manage user credentials","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To provide information about the instance itself, such as instance ID and public IP address","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage IAM roles for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure network settings for the instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the role of an EC2 instance user data script?","answers":[{"text":"To store user credentials for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To enable multi-factor authentication for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To execute commands or scripts during the launch of the instance","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage encryption keys for the instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which feature allows you to hibernate an EC2 instance and resume it from its saved state later?","answers":[{"text":"EC2 Auto Scaling","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EC2 Spot Instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EC2 Hibernate Mode","isCorrect":true},{"text":"EC2 Fleet","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of the EC2 Placement Group?","answers":[{"text":"To specify the region for the EC2 instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To group together multiple EC2 instances to achieve low-latency network performance","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To define the size of the EC2 instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure instance type for the EC2 instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of the EC2 Dedicated Host?","answers":[{"text":"To provide dedicated storage for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To allocate a dedicated public IP address to an EC2 instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To host multiple EC2 instances on a physical server with no other customers","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage EC2 instance access permissions","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which network interface type is associated with an Elastic IP address in EC2?","answers":[{"text":"Primary Network Interface","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Elastic Network Interface (ENI)","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Secondary Network Interface","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Interface","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of Amazon EC2 Spot Instances?","answers":[{"text":"To run EC2 instances in a highly available and fault-tolerant manner","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To launch EC2 instances with guaranteed capacity","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To bid for spare EC2 capacity at a potentially lower cost","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To reserve capacity for EC2 instances on-demand","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which EC2 pricing model allows you to pay for compute capacity by the second with no upfront costs or long-term commitments?","answers":[{"text":"On-Demand Instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Reserved Instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Spot Instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Dedicated Hosts","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes in the context of EC2?","answers":[{"text":"To provide temporary block-level storage for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To store data in a scalable and durable manner","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To provide scalable and high-performance block-level storage volumes for EC2 instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage EC2 instance access permissions","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the primary purpose of an EC2 Load Balancer?","answers":[{"text":"To distribute incoming network traffic across multiple EC2 instances","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To provide persistent block-level storage volumes for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To manage user identities and access to EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure network settings for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of Amazon Elastic File System (EFS) in the context of EC2?","answers":[{"text":"To store data in a scalable and durable manner","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To provide temporary block-level storage for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To manage EC2 instance access permissions","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To distribute incoming network traffic across multiple EC2 instances","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of EC2 Fleet?","answers":[{"text":"To provide dedicated storage for EC2 instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To allocate a dedicated public IP address to an EC2 instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To host multiple EC2 instances on a physical server with no other customers","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To provision and manage a fleet of EC2 instances across different instance types, Availability Zones, and purchase options","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the purpose of the EC2 Instance Metadata service?","answers":[{"text":"To store and manage user credentials","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To provide information about the instance itself, such as instance ID and public IP address","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage IAM roles for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To configure network settings for the instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"What is the role of an EC2 Instance User Data script?","answers":[{"text":"To store user credentials for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To enable multi-factor authentication for the instance","isCorrect":false},{"text":"To execute commands or scripts during the launch of the instance","isCorrect":true},{"text":"To manage encryption keys for the instance","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Which feature allows you to hibernate an EC2 instance and resume it from its saved state later?","answers":[{"text":"EC2 Auto Scaling","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EC2 Spot Instances","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EC2 Hibernate Mode","isCorrect":true},{"text":"EC2 Fleet","isCorrect":false}]}]')}}]);